Guide to the Sheri Martinelli Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- August 1999 Acquisition, 1905-1993; 114.5; (127 boxes)+ 13 art, 1 broadside, 1 roll
  - Audiocassettes and Microcassettes, 1979-1993; Series VI; 78; (78 boxes)
    - Notes and materials associated with tapes
      - Notes for boxes 65-112, undated; 48 (Box 60)
      - Notes for boxes 113-140, undated; 32 (Box 61)
      - Empty take up reel, undated
      - Earphones, empty tape boxes, undated
      - Splicing tape, undated
    - Audiocassettes
      - "Seeking 3-in-1", undated; 1 (Box 62)
        Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Joseph Campbell: Tibetan Book of the Dead, Groff Workshop May 1981, 1988; 1
      - Joseph Campbell at 80, The Hero's Journey March 1984, 75' San Francisco Celebration, 1991; 1
      - Joseph Campbell: Hermes, Alchemy, and Voyage of Odysseus #2960 1971 Esalen, 1988; 1
      - "DG visit", undated; 1
      - "Finish of DG", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "June 8/78 Thursday to DG, Sheri", 1978 June 8; 1
      - "New Age 1", undated; 1
      - "New Age 2", undated; 1
      - "New Age 3", undated; 1
      - "Act of T/[diamond], tape not too clear", undated; 1
      - "Talk SM", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Late Talk", undated; 1
      - "EP Jeuri", undated; 1
      - "Ep fr Jeroe", undated; 1
      - "St", undated; 1
      - "St?", undated; 1
      - "St what I wore", undated; 1
      - "LA M/S", undated; 1 (Box 63)
      - "USA Kulch", undated; 1
      - Nature's Agenda, Sun-Tel, Wash Post 24-91", 1991; 1
      - "P #1", undated; 1
      - "P #2", undated; 1
      - "P #3", undated; 1
      - "P 5th try, 3/29/89 Wed.", 1989 March 29; 1
      - "2nd try P", undated; 1
      - "P", undated; 1
      - "P HH N/Buick", undated; 1
      - "Poem with Vivaldi", undated; 1
      - "T/B[or]t card and SM talk", undated; 1
      - "SM talk", undated; 1
      - "On learning T/ Canciones de mi Padre, words to all/copy", undated; 1
      - "R man HH' food, Mon", 1991 February 1; 1
      - "Erase", undated; 1
      - "P", undated; 1
      - "Test D", undated; 2
      - "3", undated; 1
      - "4", undated; 1
      - "5", undated; 1 (Box 64)
      - "6", undated; 1
      - "Talk p[?] to P on tape", undated; 1
      - "P/ump", undated; 1
      - "P 1/2/91 Wed", 1991 January 2; 1
      - "Joseph Campbell Myths Through Time, T/grail, History Ch. 26/Fri", 1991 December 20; 1
      - "P and JW Pub. EP Lg Bks T/problem/ Talk by B/4", 1990 December 29; 1
      - "Voodoo", undated; 2
      - "Complaint P/St", undated; 1
      - "P Monday 2/11/91", 1991 February 11; 1
      - "P", undated; 3
      - "P and E", undated; 1
      - "DMP", undated; 1
      - "Went [fain?], undated; 1
      - "To DG late at night", undated; 1
      - "?", undated; 1
      - "Coy Hyme", undated; 1
      - "[Dde?]P original side talk", undated; 1
      - "To Diane DiPrima, made outside in sun and air, original/Private to D DP talk", undated; 1 (Box 65)
      - "To Diane DiPrima, Bryant's copy", undated; 1
      - "P/E talk", undated; 1
      - "JE F/Social order", undated; 1
      - "Social order, original copy erased", undated; 1
      - "SM=Myth Sun 12/23/90", 1990 December 23; 1
      - "Sunday Dec 23 1990 Am "talk" I also etc. Pix", 1990 December 23; 1
      - "Delta gor", undated; 1
      - "Copy with originals", undated; 1
      - "Talk what Dave said", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "P/E", undated; 1
      - [Illegible], undated; 1
      - "JJ dreams/original", undated; 1
      - "Copy of JJ dreams for J&J", undated; 1
      - "Naguas", undated; 1
      - "To AG/Cantos ESP", undated; 1
      - "Wolves sound effects", undated; 1
      - "B/LIB", undated; 1
      - "SM talk Feb end/March begin", 1991 March; 1
      - "P SM talk", undated; 1 (Box 66)
      - "Olivia B. Smith 12-10-90 8 am", 1990 December 10; 1
      - "Olivia", undated; 1
      - "Talk", undated; 1
      - "[Dr]", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Talk to Russ Uran and Sherwin destiny", undated; 1
      - "al-KHWARIZIMI c/90 EP", undated; 1
      - "Destiny notes talk to Russ, confused for TC but not entirely, J'Neller", undated; 1
      - "Sort of protest of V [legit?] before they did, Russ beings @ end", undated; 1
      - "W[ish?] dict", undated; 1
      - "Rabbi Hillel reading- ends suddenly", undated; 1
      - "Destiny Matza, Melevaste reading", undated; 1
      - "Destiny tape edited", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Joseph Campbell/ Myths Through Time Ch 26 Friday 13 - Dec '91", 1991 December 13; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - The New Awakening Introduction, 1989; 1
      - Health Imaging, Maximize Your Immunity Against Disease, 1984; 1
      - Health & Rejuvenation by Hypnosis, Discovering the Fountain of Youth, 1989-1990; 1
      - "HD 9/15/92 for Boci "T/islands", 1992 September 15; 1 (Box 67)
      - "HD#2 SM 9/15/92", 1992 September 15; 1
      - "HD and vit C 7/2/92 orig.", 1992 July 2; 1
      - "HD and vit C 7/2/92", 1991 July 2; 1
      - "Kissing Wolf for HD and of summer solstice Sun. June 21- 1992", 1992 June 21; 1
      - "Kissing Wolf summer solstice HD Sun 6-2+92", 1992 June 2; 1
      - "WAS going BE/BOCI/HD some HD on it/ G interrupts Sunday 7/12/92", 1992 July 12; 1
      - "HD #1", undated; 1
      - "HD #2", undated; 1
      - "Maria and Ball Shytle Thurs. 9/17/92", 1992 September 17; 1
      - "Wrong was on 'dubbed' or 'tape' dubbed stuck should/play", undated; 1
      - "DP Warneve", undated; 1
      - "God/IS/ON/T/MT 10 pm Monday 6/14/93", 1993 June 14; 1
      - "Monday 7/93, 6 AM Preacher", 1993 July; 1
      - "Warden call SM talk re: Neise Barrier August 21, 1992", 1992 August 21; 1
      - "SM talk and some dog bark warden here", undated; 1
      - "Copied/noisy", undated; 1
      - "Dog bark copy", undated; 1
      - "On tape with visit time/bark", undated; 1
      - "Dog bark", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Dog barking every day all day for past week to 10 days, June 3, 1992", 1992 June 3; 1 (Box 68)
      - "Dog bark 7/2/92", 1992 July 2; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - Creative Decision Making, 1990; 1
      - Recapture Youthful Vigor: Super Consciousness, subliminal persuasion self-hypnosis tapes by Potentials Unlimited, 1989; 1
      - "Your Upward Tape Daily", undated; 1
      - "Scrolls Thursday May 7, 1992", 1992 May 7; 1
      - "Synopsis, Maria fence cut/rooms old dest/wk: ABT July 5-12 1992", 1992 July 5; 1
      - "Daily Notes: Tape 4, Wednesday-Friday June 24-26, 1992", 1992 June 24; 1
      - "Supervising paper trash #5", 1992 July 2; 1
      - "Maria's School probably dialogue at Roy Rogers evening 7/18/92", 1992 July 18; 1
      - "After Sunday August 23, 1992 phone call to California talk re: neighborhood and house", 1
      - "Monday 6/14/93 #1", 1993 June 14; 1
      - "Monday 6/14/93 #2", 1993 June 14; 1
      - "Delta G Sunday, All Kids Things #1", 1993 July 11; 1
      - "Terr 8 AM 6/24/93 Ric/Vic "Bonj. Minor Yank tramel SM", 1993 June 24; 1
      - "Saturday 7/10/93, Delta G re BOCI near 3 pm", 1993 July 10; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Delta G Tuesday 5/18/93", 1993 May 18; 1
      - "SM i.e. Sheri Martinelli re:", undated; 1
      - "On tape, thurs 7/6/89", 1989 July 6; 1
      - "Delta G #2, Sunday 7/11/93 "All Kinds Things", 1993 July 11; 1 (Box 69)
      - "Tuesday July 13, 1993 Deodaktos process/personal", 1993 July 13; 1
      - "Baby/bathwater 7/9/93, King Lir", 1993 July 9; 1
      - "BACI #1", undated; 1
      - "BACI SM talk", undated; 1
      - "Tuesday July 13, 1993 BOCI papers", 1993 July 13; 1
      - "Blue Sky/Wildcat", undated; 1
      - "Letters about R/S #1", 1990 February 24; 1
      - "4#", undated; 1
      - "#3 after half through noise stops", undated; 1
      - "Noise and taped to here #2", undated; 1
      - "Talk to P, see EP/ [?]fervuly and Tibet", undated; 1
      - "MM/S Friday May 22, 1987", 1987 May 22; 1
      - "Name Sheri/ends/drift/mist Tale-no time, more takes", 1989 July 1; 1
      - "Archive of American Art day/+ notes to self SM", undated; 1
      - "They/answer R/P. Sat February 10, 1990", 1990 February 10; 1
      - "Was on tape", undated; 1
      - "#1 P T/letter and T/case, April 27, 1990", 1990 April 27; 1
      - "P/gen ideas of T/case", 1959-1960; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "#1?", undated; 1
      - "#2", undated; 1 (Box 70)
      - "Fone/lawyer Webb at heg 1pm 11/15/90", 1990 November 15; 1
      - "Want Clean Bill of Health G/M/CAL", undated; 1
      - "Fone\Gladys January 12, 1991 12 AM Murry Ricon way to here/EP items", 1991 January 12; 1
      - "Fone SM/Marcella 12/29/90 12 noon", 1990 December 29; 1
      - "Fone Gladys and M Sunday 1/20/91", 1991 January 20; 1
      - "Fone #1", 1990 November 8; 1
      - "Fone #2, Doughie Anderson, Squawk, Wet Hen", 1990 November; 1
      - "Fone #3", undated; 1
      - "Fone #4 M+Barbara D/G + Barb D week 11-30 etc. 90", 1990 November; 1
      - "Fone #5", 1990; 1
      - "Friday at 6t 7pm phone police + SM comments", undated; 1
      - "T B/B + police etc. Tuesday 3/31/92 Phone calls", 1992 March 31; 1
      - "TV Music re B/Ball + police etc. SM talk Mon.", 1992 March 30; 1
      - "B/B Police Matter Monday", 1992 March 30; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - Sample sales calls, undated; 1
      - "Friday attempt to discuss problem w/G day M+G fone", 1992 June 5; 1
      - "Copied fone, I have spoken and SM sentiments/These notes from yest etc...and SM oration "I have Spoken", undated; 1
      - "G+S discuss house etc.", 1992 June 6; 1
      - "SM + GW talk re: info on house Fri.", 1992 June 12; 1
      - "On tape?", undated; 1 (Box 71)
      - "B/Leh", undated; 1
      - "B/Leh T", undated; 1
      - "T B Leh", undated; 1
      - "To Yale Sun RWF Tape #1", 1987 April 4; 1
      - "Rest on video copied some Blih BP SM", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Canto 75", undated; 1
      - "On tape", undated; 1
      - "To BUC' and company", undated; 1
      - "IP mon", undated; 1
      - "C/75 Catherine via P/B", undated; 1
      - "To T/G copy", undated; 1
      - "Delta G 1/1/90", 1990 January 1; 1
      - "P/answer", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "File L\edge, not go in record", undated; 1
      - "P/to here check", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "T/flag", undated; 1 (Box 72)
      - "Flag Prayer", undated; 1
      - "P/Tues./Snow", 1989 December 12; 1
      - "To P/tears for EP after mind state negotiation of gt flight and antennae of race", undated; 1
      - "More to P/tonight Tuesday: how I became ill", 1989 August 15; 1
      - "P/August 31, 1989", 1989 August 31; 1
      - "P or E", undated; 1
      - "P #3 of 3 tapes", 1989 August; 1
      - "P/S/ talk", undated; 1
      - "P/talk", undated; 1
      - "HD/23000/I am Yesterday/Thursday/Sept 7, 1989/I know tomorrow", 1
      - "HD/etc.", undated; 1
      - "S+M 9/17/88 sticks be careful", 1988 September 17; 1
      - "S+M 10/10/88", 1988 October 10; 1
      - "Penalty charge", undated; 1
      - "G/argue", undated; 1
      - "G+S case", 1992 March 1; 1
      - "G+S T/case", 1992; 1
      - "First attempt to answer A times Art", undated; 1
      - "Antheil reading", undated; 1
      - "Gr alphabet", undated; 1
      - "Carp Bk", undated; 1 (Box 73)
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - P/+ Tx +check etc./idea EP stuff "2A", undated; 1
      - "P/+Tx\check etc. 2A", undated; 1
      - "re/E/Dec 2/90 Dec 2, 90 Sun G+M Cal", 1990 December 2; 1
      - "On tape?", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Time on phone to P on tape Sunday 25, 1990", 1
      - "Listen on tape", undated; 1
      - "Cant out", undated; 1
      - "Wanda/orig", undated; 1
      - "P on tape but check", undated; 1
      - "P/#1", undated; 1
      - "P/challenge", undated; 1
      - "P #2", undated; 1
      - "Hand saw May 10, 1990 SM to P/as go through day", 1990 May 10; 1
      - "Threats slander invasion of privacy", undated; 1
      - "Three house case #1 Threats to life", undated; 1
      - "House case #2", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "P/general on tape", undated; 1 (Box 74)
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Listen\change", undated; 1
      - "Cont'd from tape: first try", undated; 1
      - "3/7/90, 3/6/90", 1990 March; 1
      - "Pete/Fla. 3/23/87 My Day By Sheri", 1987 March 23; 1
      - "P P2", undated; 1
      - "Catch All", undated; 1
      - "P/Pan Pipes 3/24/87", 1987 March 24; 1
      - "P/E T/Pipes of Pan and Sheri", 1987 March 24; 1
      - "SM's copy original see EP [illegible] re combos", 1987 March 30; 1
      - "Tibet SM's original", undated; 1
      - "EP/Kon Thrust Hag Don, etc. called Gladys day/Tuesday 11/13/90 #1", 1990 November 13; 1
      - "EP etc. Hag Don 11/13/90 #2", 1990 November 13; 1
      - "M/F SM", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "Worlds etc", undated; 1
      - "SM poems world et. 2 new/+1 old first reading original 5/28/87", 1987 May 28; 1
      - "House regulations P", undated; 1
      - "Sticks here at door at out window", undated; 1
      - "New take re _out of door_ explanation G Jackal E re poison food, Thursday evening 6/14/90", 1990 June 14; 1 (Box 75)
      - "To L'/#1", undated; 1
      - "L #2", undated; 1
      - "T2 & L", undated; 1
      - "He calls, I hang up, and then/L #3", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 4
      - "New Age 6/25/88", 1988 June 25; 1
      - "An egg", undated; 1
      - "Commentary to air egg", undated; 1
      - "J1", undated; 1
      - "w/lawn NIP", undated; 1
      - "Queen", undated; 1
      - "Talk", undated; 1
      - "Talk U+vision 2 SM life", undated; 1
      - "Testing Song", undated; 1
      - " L. Mc. M, Mc.M Georgetown Larry", 1986 July 1; 1
      - "1 B/J/F/listen keeps Stopn February 18, 1985", 1985 February 18; 1
      - "1 EP/C/90", 1990; 1
      - "6/27/86 Fri. estate", 1986 June 27; 1 (Box 76)
      - "Sunday 6/29/86, 6/26/86", 1986 June 26; 1
      - "ENG 6/22/86-6/21/86 Saturday and Sunday (altar)", 1986 June; 1
      - "6/22/86 in T/nature of advertising keep cantos alive", 1986 June 22; 1
      - "ENG Kundalini", undated; 1
      - "Thursday 6/26/86 T/Cantos /general statements", 1986 June 26; 1
      - "2/27/86? 6/26 L/M Friday copy/ first tape on Thursday", 1986 February 27; 1
      - "6/27/86 Friday T/Cantos", 1986 June 27; 1
      - 6/27/86 Friday copy of T/Cantos, 1986 June 27; 1
      - "MSB + SM/via phone end flat statements", 1986 June 27; 1
      - "Pia Maz P14 winter 92\7:20 AM, Wednesday 3/24/93, grey cold chill day", 1992; 1
      - "Listen? on tape", undated; 1
      - "? Listen", undated; 1
      - "Wednesday 24/3/93 6 at 66 self chats listen, copy, or erase", 1993 March 24; 1
      - "To T/Emerald Isle Wednesday 3/24/93", 1993 March 24; 1
      - "SM talk check re: details of her story", 1993 March 18; 1
      - "Art/Chief Sealeash", undated; 1
      - "Her Story 7-8 AM Monday", 1993 March 8; 1
      - "3/8/93 #2", 1993 March 8; 1
      - "3/8/93 #3", 1993 March 8; 1
      - "#1", undated; 1
      - "#2", undated; 1 (Box 77)
      - "Megidian T.V. 10/18/92", 1992 October 18; 1
      - "Bad recording Friday 8/1/93 Preacher batteries weak", 1993 August 1; 1
      - "T.V. last one ch. 26, Sunday 11/15/92", 1992 November 15; 1
      - "Indian Pow Wow both sides, Sunday 11/14/92", 1992 November 14; 1
      - "Indian Program T.V.", undated; 1
      - "T Compartment", undated; 1
      - "T", undated; 1
      - "SM talk re Life, etc. Tuesday January 5, 1993 #1", 1993 January 5; 1
      - "SM talk re Life, etc. Tuesday January 5, 1993 #2", 1993 January 5; 1
      - "c/117 SM Wed 1/21/93", 1993 January 12; 1
      - "Prez", 1993 January 22; 1
      - "fr delta H/delta Gor S and Co, Thursday 3/4/93", 1993 March 4; 1
      - "fr delta H/delta Gor #2", undated; 1
      - "Battery goes low at end and re-do, Saturday 3/6/93, z #1", 1993 March 6; 1
      - "Z #2", undated; 1
      - "Z #3", undated; 1
      - "Account of father, Friday Jan 22, 1993 self-portrait of WOT It Feels A Word Painting", 1993 January 22; 1
      - "Erase listen 24/4/93", 1993 April 4; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "On tape", undated; 2 (Box 78)
      - "On tape #2", undated; 1
      - "Rus Psych T.V.", undated; 1
      - "SM talk 5/1/93", 1993 May 1; 1
      - Sousa Tribute: 18 Glorious Favorites, 1989; 1
      - "T.V. L. Rstadt", undated; 1
      - "Corridos copy on tape", undated; 1
      - "Contains Corridos", undated; 1
      - "From SM to LG/Corridos", undated; 1
      - Canciones de mi Padre, Linda Ronstadt, 1987; 1
      - "Hymn to Diana - by Ben Johnson Longfellow's Hiawatha - as it should sound", undated; 1
      - "The Magic of Zamifir", 1984; 1
      - "Piaf", undated; 1
      - "BLIB/Sousa", 1985; 1
      - "Sousa erase tree", undated; 1
      - "Cal SF Jap Man", undated; 1
      - "Delta H/Heart", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "Balks", undated; 1 (Box 79)
      - "Repair screws", undated; 1
      - "Test", undated; 1
      - "Delta G or re/wandgrasper", undated; 1
      - "Too lg", undated; 1
      - "7/16/85 Delta G'N", 1985 July 16; 1
      - "HW", undated; 1
      - "Delta 1:15 pm 7/ 12/85", 1985 July 12; 1
      - "# 3 Jaz", undated; 1
      - "Dogs", undated; 2
      - "Talk artist 6/14/88", 1988 June 14; 1
      - "1?", undated; 1
      - "X", undated; 1
      - "W.S.C. 3/29/81 High Noon Sun at creek", undated; 1
      - "Outdoor c/90 erase", undated; 1
      - "c/90 + #1 Sun-Noon 3/29/81", 1981 March 29; 1
      - "Thursday 1/7/93, SM on from Rabbits", 1993 January 7; 1
      - "Rabbits", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "#1", undated; 1 (Box 80)
      - [Illegible], undated; 1
      - "Pzia 7/20/81 Monday 5:30 PM Eastern Standard Time", 1981 July 20; 1
      - "Pzia", undated; 1
      - "Pzia 7/6/81", 1981 July 6; 1
      - "SM kid ways", undated; 1
      - "Some to D'yell 9/13/88", 1988; 1
      - "9/1/88 Tape tangles repaired Thursday", 1988 September 1; 1
      - "Erase", undated; 1
      - "Erase tape #2", undated; 1
      - "July 4/81 - tape stuck", 1981 July 4; 1
      - "July 4/ v. ill tape stuck", undated; 1
      - "CH, Tues #2", 1981 July 14; 1
      - "Editied fu a tape", 1981 July 1; 1
      - "CDH", 1981 July 1; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 6
      - "CDH first attempt", undated; 1 (Box 81)
      - "GH Too Much Again second attempt", undated; 1
      - "Half-erased", undated; 1
      - "Delta", undated; 2
      - "Dog bark/Do ugh tape Tuesday 6/7/88", 1988 June 7; 1
      - "Sharon If [?]", undated; 1
      - "Sharon Music Talk", undated; 1
      - "SM anti-semitism Ag 18/1992", 1992 August 18; 1
      - "EP/Tx's", undated; 1
      - "EP/R. Radio on tape/ blank so far", undated; 1
      - "Delta G 5/24/93 re: next door", 1993 May 24; 1
      - The Winning Edge: Your Key to Greater Success, 1983; 1
      - "Voices v/score/to JAZ", undated; 1
      - "SOMA", undated; 1
      - "J1", undated; 1
      - "JAZ + Talk #2", undated; 1
      - "T/3 original MMS Charlie Parker death", undated; 1
      - "66 Monday 3/8/93 6 am-7 am", 1993 March 8; 1
      - "T.V.", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 1
      - "NYC Bankers Party", undated; 1 (Box 82)
      - "2/26/82 #1", 1982 February 26; 1
      - "2/26/82 #2", 1982 February 26; 1
      - "2/26/82 #3", 1982 February 26; 1
      - "As if to JAZ", undated; 1
      - "JAZ Zen 4 etc.", undated; 1
      - "Delta #1", undated; 1
      - "JAZ and talk", undated; 1
      - "St. M", undated; 1
      - "JW pub to insert", undated; 1
      - "Eng 7/13/85 10:45 pm", 1985 July 13; 1
      - "7/11/85 12:45 pm", 1985 July 11; 1
      - "Copy to St", undated; 1
      - "Sunday sermon 3/7/82", 1982 March 7; 1
      - "Sunday #1", undated; 1
      - "[Sunday?] #2, undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 5
      - "Preacher teacher 1/22/93", 1993 January 22; 1 (Box 83)
      - "Channel 66, Monday 1/11/93 6 am preacher", 1993 January 11; 1
      - "Rabbits, Preacher 66/Jan 5/93", 1993 January 6; 1
      - "Preacher 66, Jan /5/93", 1993 January 5; 1
      - "To Self", undated; 1
      - "My "American Education" #1 SM 7/30/89 Mon", 1989 July 30; 1
      - "My "American Education" #2", 1989; 1
      - "MM Phone #", undated; 1
      - "MM art letters 3/30/87", 1987 March 30; 1
      - "Dan'yell", undated; 1
      - "Tytell Feb 23 87", 1987 February 23; 2
      - "JAS", undated; 1
      - "P1", undated; 1
      - "P #2", undated; 1
      - "P/from SM tape and tape 1/2 Church Dope Ovid", undated; 1
      - "Commentary on tape 2/12/87-P", 1987 February 12; 1
      - "P/ Tape original", undated; 1
      - "P + Notes", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 2
      - "P/copy letter to Sothebys re: papers", 1987 February 13; 1 (Box 84)
      - "Rough outline P+S's", undated; 1
      - "T/scene of T/Judge at unemployment Saturday October 23, 1982", 1982 October 23; 1
      - "After T/scene at D'slide", undated; 1
      - "D'slide scene 6/8/82 check", 1982 June 8; 1
      - "Delta G 10/24/82", 1982 October 24; 1
      - "Delta G", undated; 2
      - "10/24/82 From SM re: items EP etc. To C.L. Robinson (Bks)", 1982 October 24; 1
      - "11/11/82/ Delta G/Vet day", 1982 November 11; 1
      - "Scribble tape Delta G C/99 Passover judgement", undated; 1
      - "Copy/erase", undated; 1
      - "Copy tape Saturday 11/13/82 copy from bottom Delta G vet tape and clear vet", 1982 November 13; 1
      - "G/SM talk prayer daily 9:20 AM Feb 20, 1981", 1981 February 20; 1
      - "?", undated; 1
      - "Letter to Mary", undated; 1
      - "M", undated; 1
      - "To Mother 11/25/81", 1981 November 25; 1
      - "Mother 11/25/81", 1981 November 25; 1
      - "Mother October 21, 1982 7:30 pm Thurs", 1982 October 21; 1
      - "M", undated; 1
      - "Copy from listening to T/recent tapes w/ JAZ' [Illegible]", undated; 1 (Box 85)
      - "Y Jaz personal notes to self on tape", undated; 1
      - "Monday Dec. 2, 1985 Rose of all creation", 1985 December 2; 1
      - "7:15 pm 7/13/85 Saturday poetry J", 1985 July 13; 1
      - "Pine Grove? no it's T/Scott", undated; 1
      - "Paradisial Mind State", undated; 1
      - "P SM EP Noh play", undated; 1
      - "SM read for self pine grove contemplation and talk", undated; 1
      - "Helen talk to self", undated; 1
      - "P #1", undated; 1
      - "P and co SM talk Mind Carved [?]", undated; 1
      - "P Straight Talk #2", undated; 1
      - "P #3", undated; 1
      - "Copy MM's 1 HD etc. May 22, 1987", 1987 May 22; 1
      - "T/Cantos", undated; 1
      - "P/", undated; 1
      - "P talk poem", undated; 1
      - [Illegible] "7/9/85 Tuesday Va", 1985; 1
      - "To Mother and H and male voice at End", undated; 1
      - "At DDS 6/27/79", 1979 June 27; 1
      - "6/21/79- en route to DDS and then Big Argument", 1979 June 21; 1
      - "M/F God Love", undated; 1 (Box 86)
      - "M/F 1 Love God S/copy", undated; 1
      - "God/Love St CAtherine too She", undated; 1
      - "SM to M/M/Sothebys 2/13/87 Friday Answer to letters this AM", 1987 February 13; 1
      - "Sotheby's letter 2/13/87 Friday original", 1987 February 13; 1
      - "MM talk", undated; 1
      - "Notes on T/cantos copy of original 4/ JAZ", 1985 September; 1
      - "Notes on D cantos 4 Jaz", undated; 1
      - "Erase", undated; 1
      - "My Day 11/9/78 Thursday", 1978 November 9; 1
      - "MM/S's SM 5/25/87", 1987 May 25; 1
      - "Charles edit", undated; 1
      - "Ch and Co", undated; 1
      - "Home phone speak [?] to G", undated; 1
      - "Sat May 26/76 @ [illegible]", 1979 Saturday 26; 1
      - "geo/home", undated; 1
      - 1/2, undated; 1
      - "3", undated; 1
      - [Unlabeled], undated; 3
      - "Cantos notes 1 beautiful day", undated; 1 (Box 87)